Have you ever loved a TV show?
你曾经热爱过一部电视剧吗？
I mean really loved it?
我是说真的热爱？
Like, you can't wait to get to work to talk about it loved it?
就像，你迫不及待地想去上班，就为了和别人谈论它的那种热爱？
What about the cliffhanger?
那扣人心弦的悬念呢？
That‘s the unresolved situation at the end of the episode which makes you want to watch the next one.
就是一集结尾处那个悬而未决的情节，让你忍不住想看下一集。
But, when will the next one be?
但是，下一集什么时候才会播出呢？
In the past, viewers had to wait up to a week for the next episode of their favourite shows.
在过去，观众们不得不等上长达一周的时间，才能看到他们最喜欢的电视剧的下一集。
What agony!
这是多么痛苦啊！
But, that's not the case any more.
但是，现在情况不再是这样了。
And hand in hand with that comes a, possibly dangerous, growing social trend.
与此同时，一种可能危险的、日益增长的社会趋势也随之而来。
We speak of binge-watching.
我们把它叫做疯狂追剧。
Binge-watching is when a person watches more than one episode of a show in quick succession.
疯狂追剧指的是一个人接连不断地观看一部电视剧的多集内容。
With developments in the speed and connectivity of the internet, increases in technology and the rise of on-demand entertainment companies, people can now have their favourite shows streamed directly to their television at their convenience.
随着互联网网速和连接性的发展、技术的进步以及点播娱乐公司的兴起，人们现在可以在方便的时候，将他们喜欢的电视剧直接流式传输到他们的电视上观看。
This behaviour is nothing new.
这种行为并不是什么新鲜事。
In fact, 'binge-watching' has been officially listed in dictionaries since 2015.
事实上，“疯狂追剧”自2015年起就已被正式收录进词典。
The entertainment companies recognise this behaviour and many take steps to encourage it.
娱乐公司认识到了这种行为，并且很多公司都采取措施来鼓励它。
Often, instead of releasing each episode on a week-by-week basis, an entire series will become available concurrently.
通常，一整部电视剧会同时上线，而不是每周播出一集。
Once the episode finishes, many platforms will display pop-ups with 'you might like' suggestions, or will automatically play the next episode.
一集结束后，许多平台会显示带有“你可能喜欢”推荐内容的弹出窗口，或者会自动播放下一集。
However, this wondrous gift may in fact be a poisoned chalice.
然而，这份奇妙的礼物实际上可能是一个看似诱人实则有害的事物。
Recent research from British media watchdog Ofcom suggests that this behaviour may have become a hindrance.
英国媒体监管机构英国通信管理局最近的研究表明，这种行为可能已经成为了一种阻碍。
Out of the more than half of British adults who watch more than one episode of a show back-to-back, almost a third have admitted missing sleep or becoming tired as a result; and one quarter have neglected their household chores.
在超过一半连续观看多集电视剧的英国成年人中，几乎三分之一的人承认因此而睡眠不足或感到疲惫；四分之一的人忽视了他们的家务。
Next we'll be missing work!
接下来我们可能连工作都要耽误了！
Bingeing has other connections — binge eating, binge drinking and binge smoking.
疯狂追剧还与其他行为有关——暴饮暴食、酗酒和大量吸烟。
All of which are often associated with compulsive behaviour, a lack of control and a possible route to addiction.
所有这些行为通常都与强迫性行为、缺乏自控力以及可能导致成瘾相关。
Lindsey Fussell, consumer group director at Ofcom, said: "The days of waiting a week for the next episode are largely gone, with people finding it hard to resist watching multiple episodes around the house or on the move."
英国通信管理局的消费者团体主管林赛·富塞尔说：“等上一周看下一集的日子在很大程度上已经一去不复返了，人们发现无论是在家里还是在外出途中，都很难抗拒连续观看多集电视剧。”
If people find binge-watching hard to resist, coupled with the fact that it has shown to lead to negligence in many, are we witnessing the birth of a new type of addiction?
如果人们发现疯狂追剧难以抗拒，再加上它已经被证明会导致很多人做事粗心大意，那么我们是否正在见证一种新型成瘾行为的诞生呢？
The myriad of information and entertainment that television and online media can bring us is, many would say, a good thing.
许多人会说，电视和网络媒体能够带给我们的海量的信息和娱乐是一件好事。
It offers us opportunities to better understand the world we live in, educate ourselves and enjoy much needed downtime.
它为我们提供了更好地了解我们所生活的世界、自我教育以及享受非常需要的休闲时光的机会。
However, like any behaviour done to excess, it can become dangerous.
然而，就像任何过度的行为一样，它也可能变得危险。
And when the activity begins to bleed into other areas, causing us to stop functioning — then it becomes a problem.
当这种行为开始渗透到其他领域，导致我们无法正常生活时——那么它就成了一个问题。
So, what's the answer?
那么，解决办法是什么呢？
Moderation!
适度！
Neither a tiny amount, nor too much.
既不要太少，也不要太多。
After all, as the old proverb says... a little of what you fancy does you good.
毕竟，正如那句古老的谚语所说......喜欢的东西，稍微享受一点对你有好处。